

FLUTTER DEVELOPER







+91 9656410682

#### Skills

Mobile App development

Backend (Firebase & AWS)

Android, IOS

Git

**UX** Design

### I'm a developer who...

2+ years of experience in interface/mobile app development across-platform. In my experience, I was able to develop a complete mobile app. I'm passionate about converting the design into code and user experience research to ensure quality.

#### Software

Visual Studio
Android Studio
Firebase
AWS

Github

Figma

#### **Education**

**Computer Science** 

2019 - 2021 (Plus Two)

Bachelor of computer application

2021 - Present

Amity University Noida

# **Live Projects**

Food ordering App 7

## Experience

Flutter developer @PayNav
Remote (March 2022 - Present)

Freelancer - Flutter developer

Remote (February 2020 - February 2022)

- Followed client's vision and meet their exact needs in order to deliver that dream come true result.
- Completed 10+ real projects in different field.
- Build the client's exact vision into code and quality.
- Provided the best mobile user experience.
- Worked in e-commerce projects.
- Integrate animations into the app projects with the requirement.
- Delivered the most optimized code that improves the performance.

# **Projects**

Project Name : Food Ordering App

Technology used : Flutter, Firebase

Role : Developer

Responsibility : Handle both frontend and backend, Integrated with Google sheet and Firebase.

Project description : Android app for order a food item from the baking industry. List out the

available menu, price, image, and description. Customer can order food directly from this app. On another side, there will be an app admin to manage the orders that are coming from the customer, and the order auto-generates orders into the different delivery sheets by the order comes. App work as order receiver

and generates delivery sheets for the baking industry.

Project Name : Product Management System

Technology used : Flutter, Firebase

Role : Developer

Responsibility : Handle both front end and backend, Integrated Firebase.

Project description : Product Management System used to view stock details. List out the menu that

is available, price, image, and description for customers. Able to find each

product's detiles by scanning QR code.

Project Name : Music Streaming App

Technology used : Flutter, Hive, Firebase

Role : Developer

Responsibility : Create Music application with flutter and backend in firebase and jioSaavn API

Project description : Android and IOS app for streaming, downloading, and sharing music for free. we

can search for the latest song, Able to download any song. On another, we can

play our own songs. and customize our playlist also.